[
	{
		"id": "1",
		"question": "गुलाबी",
		"answer": "pink"
	},
	{
		"id": "2",
		"question": "काला",
		"answer": "black"
	},
	{
		"id": "3",
		"question": "सफेद",
		"answer": "white"
	},
	{
		"id": "3",
		"question": "लाल",
		"answer": "red"
	},
	{
		"id": "4",
		"question": "नीला",
		"answer": "blue"
	},
	{
		"id": "5",
		"question": "पीला",
		"answer": "yellow"
	},
	{
		"id": "6",
		"question": "नारंगी",
		"answer": "orange"
	},
	{
		"id": "7",
		"question": "हरा",
		"answer": "green"
	},
	{
		"id": "8",
		"question": "नीलम",
		"answer": "indigo"
	},
	{
		"id": "9",
		"question": "केसरी",
		"answer": "saffron"
	},
	{
		"id": "10",
		"question": "बैंगनी",
		"answer": "purple"
	},
	{
		"id": "11",
		"question": "भूरा",
		"answer": "brown"
	},
	{
		"id": "12",
		"question": "धूसर",
		"answer": "grey"
	}
]
